<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Strichliste ‒ The Tally Sheet Replacement for Your Organization</title>
    <link>https://www.strichliste.org/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Strichliste ‒ The Tally Sheet Replacement for Your Organization</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 04 Feb 2019 16:00:32 +0100</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://www.strichliste.org/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>LDAP Importer</title>
      <link>https://www.strichliste.org/news/ldapimport/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Feb 2019 16:00:32 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.strichliste.org/news/ldapimport/</guid>
      <description>Strichliste just got a new, experimental command! You can now import users from a LDAP source. See the documentation here at our Commands.md for more details!
You can also let this run as a cronjob to update the users mailaddress or create new ones as they appear in your LDAP directory.
Feedback is appreciated!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Strichliste 2 released!</title>
      <link>https://www.strichliste.org/news/strichliste2/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 21 Dec 2018 08:59:19 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.strichliste.org/news/strichliste2/</guid>
      <description>After a lot of concept work, strichliste 2 has now a stable API and also a well designed front-end. We&amp;rsquo;ve also changed our tech stack completely. Instead of node.js in the backend, and angular js in the front-end, we&amp;rsquo;re now using a symfony based PHP backend providing the API and also command-line tools for several tasks.
The new frontend is completely responsive and uses react and redux as it&amp;rsquo;s core components.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Install strichliste</title>
      <link>https://www.strichliste.org/install/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 21 Dec 2018 00:00:08 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.strichliste.org/install/</guid>
      <description>For strichliste to run, PHP 7.1 or higher is required. You should have a webserver running which supports mod_php or php-fpm.
Installing  Go to the Github project to download the latest release. It comes already with a bundled front-end. Extract the package content to your target directory (e.g. tar xvfz strichliste.tar.gz -C /var/www/strichliste.yourdomain.tld) Move the database in var/ from app.db.example to app.db if you want to use the default sqlite setup.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Static builds are now available!</title>
      <link>https://www.strichliste.org/news/static-builds/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Jan 2016 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.strichliste.org/news/static-builds/</guid>
      <description>Now it&amp;rsquo;s easier to setup your strichliste instance, because we now provide static builds for strichliste-web! You can easily grab the latest build from github and follow the install instructions.
We&amp;rsquo;re currently working on major features. Stay tuned for the next major release</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Frequently Asked Questions</title>
      <link>https://www.strichliste.org/faq/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 02 Jan 2016 20:15:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.strichliste.org/faq/</guid>
      <description>Documentation API You can find the server API documentation right in the server repos API.md.
Commands Available commands are documented here: Commands.md
How to get in touch? IRC If you have any questions which are not answered by the Documentation, please do not hesitate to contact us: The IRC channel is irc://irc.freenode.net/strichliste.
Twitter You can also reach us at @strichliste_org on Twitter! Just follow us to get the latest news about strichliste.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>More features to come</title>
      <link>https://www.strichliste.org/news/more-features/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Nov 2015 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.strichliste.org/news/more-features/</guid>
      <description>Stay tuned for more features! We&amp;rsquo;re now working on some wanted features in the next strichliste release. These features are: money transfer, splitting bills, cancellation of the last order within a specific time range and we&amp;rsquo;re preparing the database for articles</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What is this project about?</title>
      <link>https://www.strichliste.org/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 11 Jul 2015 20:23:21 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.strichliste.org/about/</guid>
      <description>strichliste ([ʃtʀɪçˈlɪstə], German word for tally sheet) is a tool to replace a tally sheet inside a hackerspace. It&amp;rsquo;s aim is to provide a no-frills, easy-to-setup and -to-use solution for managing your organization&amp;rsquo;s snack bar. 
Demo That&amp;rsquo;s what you&amp;rsquo;re here for, right? You can access a demo of strichliste here. But, just to be sure, here&amp;rsquo;s how it looks like:
Architecture strichliste consists of two components: the frontend and the backend.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hello World</title>
      <link>https://www.strichliste.org/news/helloworld/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 11 Jul 2015 12:31:53 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.strichliste.org/news/helloworld/</guid>
      <description>strichliste has it&amp;rsquo;s own homepage now! We&amp;rsquo;re in the process of getting the content ready, stay tuned for updates.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>